[{"answer": "It's not working", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Wormhole-Xtreme.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "I mean, it's not working", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "That's exactly what I said so why aren't the aliens ever in camouflage", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Wormhole-Xtreme.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "An alien wouldn't wanna be seen, my friend. Think", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "You know what he worked on before this? A show about a talking dog who solves crimes. So what if they had a hundred episodes", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Wormhole-Xtreme.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Yes. my friend", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "The auditions are in the building over there", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Wormhole-Xtreme.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "I've got the licence plates of every vehicle that comes and goes through here on file", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "The Colonel stood before the vertical shimmering pool of light fascinated by the dancing ripples in the event horizon. What mysteries lay beyond this mystical portal, what wonders awaited him and his band of stalwart cohorts", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Wormhole-Xtreme.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Damn good", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Perimeter's secure Major. We're awaiting your orders", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Wormhole-Xtreme.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Move in. Move in", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "You think that's funny", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Wormhole-Xtreme.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "When's a good time to fade out", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Are you okay", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Wormhole-Xtreme.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "All right let's get some ice in here", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "You realise this is not a real show, right", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Wormhole-Xtreme.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "It's not a real show", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Be heroic and just look over here at.", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Wormhole-Xtreme.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "No. It's not a real show", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "This isn't a real show", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Wormhole-Xtreme.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "If it's not a real show, then why are you telling me what to do? How could this not be a real show if we're doing it? Right now", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-Wormhole-Xtreme.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I wouldn't lie to you", "qsentId": 24}]